<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>dinkurs.se</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.dinkurs.se/en/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.dinkurs.se/en</link>
	<description>Deltagarhantering och enkel administration</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 10:50:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Simplify participant registration and administration</title>
		<link>https://www.dinkurs.se/en/forenkla-deltagaranmalan-och-administration/</link>
					<comments>https://www.dinkurs.se/en/forenkla-deltagaranmalan-och-administration/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[mattias_h4d864n2]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 10:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.dinkurs.se/?p=2283</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="vc_row wpb_row vc_row-fluid"><div class="wpb_column vc_column_container vc_col-sm-12"><div class="vc_column-inner"><div class="wpb_wrapper">
	<div class="wpb_text_column wpb_content_element " >
		<div class="wpb_wrapper">
			<div id="content">
<div id="main">
<table border="0" cellspacing="0" cellpadding="0">
<tbody>
<tr>
<td valign="top">
<div id="center_col">
<div id="news">
<div class="page_content_area">
<table class="clean" border="0" cellspacing="2" cellpadding="2">
<tbody>
<tr>
<td>
<h2>Participant registration online test</h2>
<p>When you as a participant have the choice between two organizers where one receives participant registration via telephone or email and the other organizer has the registration form published on their website in where you as participant enter information and enter payment information at the time of registration, at the time of day it suits you. Which organizer would you choose?</p>
<p>There will be a big difference in workload for the participant who either needs to adapt to the organizer&#8217;s telephone times or email their details to them and wait for feedback if they have been registered and to receive payment details for participation, or where they enter the registration form via a browser and fill in the information and provide payment information where relevant.</p>
<p>But especially for the organizers&#8217; administrators, the workload can be greatly reduced. They access all information about participants and payments via their own login and also communicate with the participants if needed, updated information is sent via eg email or sms.</p>
<h2>Card payment and swish</h2>
<p>Have your customers pay at the time of registration. Increase service and reduce administration by allowing participants to pay for participation at the time of registration, either through cards or Swish. Participation fees are transferred to you on a weekly basis and a settlement fee is available through the organizer pages at Dinkurs.se. This facilitates participants, organizer administrators and economists.</p>
<h2>Invoice, GLN and e-invoice.</h2>
<p>If your customers prefer or require invoices as a means of payment, maybe they are municipalities or county councils and want e-invoices, then there is support for this.You can have unique number series for the invoices you send through Your Course. The invoices can be sent with the confirmation email when the participants register.You check the payment status on the invoices through your organizer page at Din Kurs.You can also choose that your course handles invoice monitoring, reminders and reconciliation for invoices. This is done in collaboration with our invoice partner FINQR. We also manage through FINQR, GLN numbers and e-invoices which have become the rule when you have municipalities and county councils as participants.</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
</div>
</div>

		</div>
	</div>
</div></div></div></div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.dinkurs.se/en/forenkla-deltagaranmalan-och-administration/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Simplify participant registration and administration</title>
		<link>https://www.dinkurs.se/en/simplify-participant-registration-and-administration/</link>
					<comments>https://www.dinkurs.se/en/simplify-participant-registration-and-administration/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mikael Strand]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 12:10:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.dinkurs.se/?p=1464</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Participant registration online When you as a participant have the choice between two organizers where one receives participant registration via telephone or email and the other organizer has the registration form published on their website in where you as participant enter information and enter payment information at the time of registration, at the time of &#8230; <p class="link-more"><a href="https://www.dinkurs.se/en/simplify-participant-registration-and-administration/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Simplify participant registration and administration"</span></a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div id="content">
<div id="main">
<table border="0" cellspacing="0" cellpadding="0">
<tbody>
<tr>
<td valign="top">
<div id="center_col">
<div id="news">
<div class="page_content_area">
<table class="clean" border="0" cellspacing="2" cellpadding="2">
<tbody>
<tr>
<td>
<h2>Participant registration online</h2>
<p>When you as a participant have the choice between two organizers where one receives participant registration via telephone or email and the other organizer has the registration form published on their website in where you as participant enter information and enter payment information at the time of registration, at the time of day it suits you. Which organizer would you choose?</p>
<p>There will be a big difference in workload for the participant who either needs to adapt to the organizer&#8217;s telephone times or email their details to them and wait for feedback if they have been registered and to receive payment details for participation, or where they enter the registration form via a browser and fill in the information and provide payment information where relevant.</p>
<p>But especially for the organizers&#8217; administrators, the workload can be greatly reduced. They access all information about participants and payments via their own login and also communicate with the participants if needed, updated information is sent via eg email or sms.</p>
<h2>Card payment and swish</h2>
<p>Have your customers pay at the time of registration. Increase service and reduce administration by allowing participants to pay for participation at the time of registration, either through cards or Swish. Participation fees are transferred to you on a weekly basis and a settlement fee is available through the organizer pages at Dinkurs.se. This facilitates participants, organizer administrators and economists.</p>
<h2>Invoice, GLN and e-invoice.</h2>
<p>If your customers prefer or require invoices as a means of payment, maybe they are municipalities or county councils and want e-invoices, then there is support for this.You can have unique number series for the invoices you send through Your Course. The invoices can be sent with the confirmation email when the participants register.You check the payment status on the invoices through your organizer page at Din Kurs.You can also choose that your course handles invoice monitoring, reminders and reconciliation for invoices. This is done in collaboration with our invoice partner FINQR. We also manage through FINQR, GLN numbers and e-invoices which have become the rule when you have municipalities and county councils as participants.</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
</div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.dinkurs.se/en/simplify-participant-registration-and-administration/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Vouchers</title>
		<link>https://www.dinkurs.se/en/vouchers/</link>
					<comments>https://www.dinkurs.se/en/vouchers/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mikael Strand]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 17:15:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Function List]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.dinkurs.se/?p=1462</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Vouchers can be used by the participant as payment when registering for an event. At the same time, the participant will experience it a little smoother when he registers because his contact information is filled in automatically: a 10-card, a discount (number) a monthly, term or membership card (time) a value card / gift card &#8230; <p class="link-more"><a href="https://www.dinkurs.se/en/vouchers/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Vouchers"</span></a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div id="content">
<div id="main">
<table border="0" cellspacing="0" cellpadding="0">
<tbody>
<tr>
<td valign="top">
<div id="center_col">
<div id="news">
<div class="page_content_area">
<table class="clean" border="0" cellspacing="2" cellpadding="2">
<tbody>
<tr>
<td>Vouchers can be used by the participant as payment when registering for an event. At the same time, the participant will experience it a little smoother when he registers because his contact information is filled in automatically:</p>
<ul>
<li>a 10-card, a discount (number)</li>
<li>a monthly, term or membership card (time)</li>
<li>a value card / gift card (SEK/EUR)</li>
</ul>
<p>The organizer creates their own vouchers, chooses the events to which the voucher will apply.</p>
<p>The participant buys the voucher &#8220;online&#8221; via your website. This voucher is in the form of a unique &#8220;code&#8221;. This code is included in a confirmation that is automatically sent via email when the customer has purchased their voucher. This code is then used by the customer as payment when registering for your events.</p>
<p>For the organizer, it provides flexibility and the voucher becomes part of planning the business. The organizer receives the fee for the event already when the participant buys his voucher. This is combined with the advantage of a card or swish payment in connection with the purchase.</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
</div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.dinkurs.se/en/vouchers/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Become a professional organizer with Din Kurs!</title>
		<link>https://www.dinkurs.se/en/become-a-professional-organizer-with-din-kurs/</link>
					<comments>https://www.dinkurs.se/en/become-a-professional-organizer-with-din-kurs/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mikael Strand]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 17:13:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Function List]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.dinkurs.se/?p=1460</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Would you like to improve your company&#8217;s events, courses or seminars. Do you want to be sure to get paid by the participants and also use cards as a payment option. Always get paid, and also in advance Organizers who use the card payment through Din Kurs secure the payment for each participant directly at &#8230; <p class="link-more"><a href="https://www.dinkurs.se/en/become-a-professional-organizer-with-din-kurs/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Become a professional organizer with Din Kurs!"</span></a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div id="content">
<div id="main">
<table border="0" cellspacing="0" cellpadding="0">
<tbody>
<tr>
<td valign="top">
<div id="center_col">
<div id="news">
<div class="page_content_area">
<table class="clean" border="0" cellspacing="2" cellpadding="2">
<tbody>
<tr>
<td>Would you like to improve your company&#8217;s events, courses or seminars. Do you want to be sure to get paid by the participants and also use cards as a payment option.</p>
<h2>Always get paid, and also in advance</h2>
<p>Organizers who use the card payment through Din Kurs secure the payment for each participant directly at the time of registration, participants who have difficulty with the payment do not occupy places that a good payer could have filled.</p>
<p>The collected fees are paid to you as an organizer once a week. You can when you want to print a document that contains all the information regarding the card payments as well as documents to use in your accounts.</p>
<p>We also offer invoicing and invoice purchases via Finqr.</p>
<h2>Follow-up, the way to become a professional</h2>
<p>We at Din Kurs recommend that you create an improvement plan as an organizer. This is to constantly improve the business. As part of this, Din Kurs has created a system to automatically invite participants to participate in a survey. In our survey function, you as the organizer create your own forms and questions. We would like to point out that even if the event has been successful, there are further ways to improve as an organizer.</p>
<p><strong>After one or more events with associated follow-up follow-up, you can, for example, get answers to:</strong></p>
<p>&#8211; What caught the interest of the participants the most?<br />
&#8211; What makes your event unique<br />
&#8211; What makes you unique?<br />
&#8211; What worked less well?</p>
<p>And perhaps the most important question, &#8220;How do you think we can improve?&#8221;.</p>
<p>In our system for surveys, you can easily compare different events and thereby follow the results over time to maintain and also enhance the customer experience.</p>
<p>It is easy to understand the importance of the result that answered follow-ups can give and the value of a strengthened reputation.</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
</div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.dinkurs.se/en/become-a-professional-organizer-with-din-kurs/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Invoice service now via Finqr</title>
		<link>https://www.dinkurs.se/en/finqr/</link>
					<comments>https://www.dinkurs.se/en/finqr/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[mattias_h4d864n2]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 15:05:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Function List]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://dinkurs.se.92-33-32-245.goclouded.com/?p=105</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[DinKurs has long offered our organizers invoice service. Invoice service greatly facilitates for your organizers who want to offer the participant to pay for the invoice. With our invoice monitoring, you as organizer do not have to re-conciliate the invoices with your bank and send reminders. We have now started a collaboration with Finqr. Finqr &#8230; <p class="link-more"><a href="https://www.dinkurs.se/en/finqr/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Invoice service now via Finqr"</span></a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>DinKurs has long offered our organizers invoice service. Invoice service greatly facilitates for your organizers who want to offer the participant to pay for the invoice. With our invoice monitoring, you as organizer do not have to re-conciliate the invoices with your bank and send reminders.</p>
<p>We have now started a collaboration with Finqr. Finqr is a company that not only does the type of invoice monitoring we already offer, but they do so much more.</p>
<p>FINQR is there to help you gain control and optimize your liquidity. They will help you with distribution, requirements management, financing and bookkeeping of invoices.</p>
<p>In addition, FINQR works with all financial systems. What makes them extra unique is that the platform is not based on old rigorous standards used by many dinosaurs in the industry. This means that they can be much more flexible and connect to all types of financial systems and adapt us to you.</p>
<p>We will roll out the link to FINQR for you who use our invoice service now during Q4-2019 / Q1-2020. In this work, FINQR will contact you and explain more about our cooperation.</p>
<p>During the autumn, we will also adjust our pricing for invoice service and make it more advantageous for you as a customer.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.dinkurs.se/en/finqr/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
